

Atlanta, GA

609.892.2662

msjoyjackson@gmail.com

<u>www.msjoyjackson.com</u>

in www.linkedin.com/in/joysjackson

www.github.com/joydotcom

Profile

Personable and Passionate Front End Web Developer with a background in Education and Performance Art & Design. My professional experiences require me to be flexible, juggle multiple concerns at once, and effectively communicate with my team. Attention to detail is always a top priority. I must be able to quickly assess any situation and rely on critical thinking to utilize the proper strategies and skills for problem solving – professionally and accurately. These skills I have, and continue to, successfully develop.

Experience

Web Developer, Georgia Tech (Student) – 2021

Manage teams. Develop & Present Web Applications: Front and Back End Development.

Teacher, Ben Hill Private Academy – 2019-2020

Observed, Evaluated, & Implemented Academic and Social Development, Curriculum and Lesson Planning. Collect, Analyze, & Present Student Data.

Student Development Coordinator/ Teacher, Paterson Public Schools – 2014-2019

Achieve Effective Student Development through Programing. Facilitate Professional Development for Faculty and Staff. Analyze, Prepare, and Present Evidence Data. Instruct, Organize, and Develop Performing Arts & Design Curriculum. Network with External Stakeholders.

Asst. Dir.: Nightlife Entertainment Services, Atlantic City Casinos - 2005 -2015

Assist Director with Procedures & Protocol. Oversee Services for Entertainment Guests. Analyze, Organize, & Present Data. Conduct Rehearsals for House Entertainment.

Education

Georgia Tech – Full Stack Web Development Certificate - 2021
William Paterson University – Educational Leadership Graduate Studies (18 credits) - 2018
Montclair State University - BS Kinesiology - 2008

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, VS Code, MVC, SQL Database, Glthub, Adobe Suite, Front End Design, Team Leadership, Effective Communication, Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Creativity, Organization.

References

Junghoon Yoon - jyoom3@2u.com - Instructor : Georgia Tech
Jovon Griffon - griffonj25@gmail.com - Talent Acquisitions Specialist
Tararra Hill - tararra@yahoo.com - Senior Marketing Professional